myteam11.in 2016-09-03

# Fantasy Cricket | My Team 11 | Live Cricket Score

This document refers to privacy policy and personal information safety relating to Myteam11.com and its associated services.

Myteam11.com is the forerunning brand of SVAP Infotech Private Limited (“Myteam11.com”). Myteam11.com is basically a cricket portal but it also features other online games like football and other fantasy games .

Any person who makes use of the features provided on Myteam11.com and participates in games (like fantasy games("Game"), (“Amusement Facilities”) and various contests etc. which are offered on Myteam11.com shall be bound by this Privacy Policy.

Myteam11.com also assures the privacy of its Users and is devoted to protect it in all respects. Myteam11.com offers many Amusement Facilities which will give user a nice experience so that user would like to come again. Our 'About Us' section will explain what Myteam11.com is all about and how it came into existence. Users will have to register themselves to play the fantasy games on Myteam11.com but most of the Amusement Facilities are offered for free. During registration process user will have to provide the details being asked and some information will be automatically tracked during User's navigation on Myteam11.com.

Registration

Myteam11.com has registration process. Users will have to register themselves before they start playing games and also to make use of other Facilities/Features which are offered on Myteam11.com and also on our Facebook application. During registration process users would be required to provide certain information like:

  * 1\. ID
  * 2\. Email
  * 3\. Password
  * 4\. Date of birth

User Invitations

Users may invite other Users which can be Existing or Non- Existing Users through email address or by their facebook usernames to participate in any of the Amusement Facilities and other contests provided by Myteam11.com.

Any questions or clarifications with respect to this Policy can be sent to MyTeam11.com at: sanjit@svapinfotech.com or by normal/physical mail addressed to: **C-109,Vaishali Nagar Behind Inox Cinemas, Gokul Path Jaipur,Raj.302021**

Myteam11.com will then use this information to contact the User and will invite the user to register with Myteam11.com and participate in the Fantasy Games/Amusement Facilities . The Invited User will have to abide by the Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions for participation in any of the Amusement Facilities on Myteam11.com website .

Use of Information:

The information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used to enable us to provide our services to you. Information collected is relative to Game or Amusement Facility that the user wishes to play or participate.

In addition, we may use the information for the following purposes:

  * 1\. To provide you with information requested from us, relating to our Fantasy games and Amusement Facilities
  * 2\. To improve our Amusement facilities and user-friendly game experience.
  * 3\. Password
  * 4\. To notify you about any changes to our website, such as improvements or other Amusement Facilities, that may affect our service.

We may also share some information like aggregate statistical information with advertisers or third parties to get to know about our visitors and site traffic.

Where applicable, we may disclose your personal information or share such information with third parties to assist fraud protection and minimise credit risk, providing services requested by the User, complying with legal process, and ensuring security related to our services.

Where we intend to use your personal information (like user name, email address) we will ensure that we notify you first. If you do not want us to use your data you will have the opportunity to withhold your consent for your use other than as listed above.

Collecting Information/Use of Cookies:

An HTTP cookie (also called web cookie, Internet cookie, browser cookie or simply cookie), is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored in the user's web browser while the user is browsing. Every time the user loads the website, the browser sends the cookie back to the server to notify the user's previous activity.

Cookies or similar electronic tools will be used by us to collect user information. When a user visits the website then a unique number or User Identification (User ID) is assigned so as to understand the User's individual interests. Myteam11.com has no way to know or decide who the User is, even if we assign a cookie to the User's computer. We cannot know until and unless the User voluntarily identifies himself/herself that is through registration process.

A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive that allows us to recognise your computer from one visit and from one page access to the next. This helps us to customise the Site as per your interests to reflect your individual preferences and it also allow us to understand how you and other users use the facilities and play the Fantasy Games so that we can improve our website and also the Amusement Facilities/contests provided by us.

When created, cookies normally don't contain any personal information. They don't scan your computer or do any kind of investigation to find out your personal information. Any personal information they might contain is a result of user’s own input on a website's form that is the information supplied by the User. Myteam11.com will have no control in the case where our advertisers assign their own cookies to the user's browser (which happens if the User clicks on their ad banners).

When any User visits the site then Myteam11.com's web servers will automatically collect limited information about User's computer connection to the Internet, including User's IP address,. (User's IP address is a numerical label assigned to each device participating in a computer network that uses the Internet Protocol for communication. This number allows computers attached to the Internet know where to send data to the User -- such as the web pages viewed by the User. It is similar to that someone needs your mailing address to send you a letter). The User's IP address does not reveal any personal details of user. Myteam11.com uses this information to deliver the content which the user requests and also to upgrade the functioning of website according to user interests, to analyze the site traffic and to let advertisers know the geographic locations of Myteam11.com's visitors which ultimately signifies popularity.

Myteam11.com also contains links or redirecting URL’s to other websites. Such websites follow their respective privacy policies, which are beyond Myteam11.com's control. Once the User leaves Myteam11.com's servers (the User can check the URL shown in the location bar of User's browser to know where he/she is or to know the location) then in that case use of any information provided by the User will be governed by the privacy policy of the site’s operator which the User is visiting. That policy may differ from Myteam11.com's own policy. If the User can't find any link to the privacy policy of any of these sites from the site's homepage then the User may contact the site directly for more information.

Myteam11.com may share some information with it's online advertisers to help them understand the preferences of the users who visit the website and also confirm the value of advertising on our website. It is usually in the form of aggregated statistics of traffic on various pages within our site. When you register with Myteam11.com then we contact you in a timely manner to inform you to update your content so as to provide features or any upgradations which we believe may benefit you.

Information Security:

All information which is gathered on Myteam11.com that is the one which the user submits and other also is securely stored within Myteam11.com-controlled database. The database is stored on servers which are secured by firewall and access to such servers is strictly limited and is password-protected. However, we understand that how much effective the security measures are, no security system is impenetrable or inaccessible. Thus, we cannot take guarantee of the security of database and also of the information that you transfer us over the internet as it can be intercepted or obstructed at the time of transmission over the Internet. Furthermore, any information that you post at the time of discussion over site will be public and will be available to anyone with Internet access.

Myteam11.com also believes that the internet is dynamic and ever changing medium and everyday something new is added to it. So, accordingly we may review our policies and change them time to time. Our use of any information we gather will always be consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be.

We use third-party advertisers which serve ads at the time of your visit to our website. These advertisers may use information (excluding personal details like name, address, phone number etc.) to track your visits to this and other websites to know about your interests and then they provide advertisements about goods and services of your interest. We will not reveal your personal identity in connection with the disclosure of such interest to any third party. Several fraudulent emails, websites, blogs etc. which claims to be from or associated with Myteam11.com may or are circulating on the Internet. These emails, websites, blogs etc. often include our logo, photos, links, content or other information from any of Myteam11.com. Some emails, websites, blogs etc. asks the users to provide their details like login name, password etc. or sometimes they prompt the users to enter or share their credit card details or other details by telling that that the user has won a prize/ gift of some kind. The sources and contents of these emails, websites, blogs etc. and accompanying materials are in no way associated with the Myteam11.com and Myteam11.com will not be responsible if you reply to such mails or blogs or share any information with them. For your own protection, we strongly recommend not to respond to such emails or websites or blogs etc. and also to not share any credit /debit card details with them.

Any doubts or comments with respect to this Privacy Policy can be sent to MyTeam11.com at: sanjit@svapinfotech.com or by normal/physical mail addressed to:

C-109,Vaishali Nagar Behind Inox Cinemas, Gokul Path Jaipur,Raj.302021
